This place is...
this place is Green Dolphin
Street State Prison!
And I'm...
in the hallway in front
of the visiting room!
What the hell do you want?
I didn't want to see your face.
You think you can just come
waltzing back into my life?
Don't show up acting all fatherly now!
I want to help you.
I'm gonna get you out of here soon.
Oh, shut up!
You know damn well you
can't pull that off.
Two years for a hit and run is nothing.
I can handle it fine by myself.
Just relax.
For the longest time, I've wanted to...
Keep that shit to yourself.
The last thing I need is for you
to try acting like a real father.
Go away!
What the...
Who are these two?
These people look so
similar to the others.
But they're not.
Get lost already!
I don't get along with you, remember?
What is going on?
We were just in Cape
Canaveral a minute ago.
And also, for that matter...
Just when the heck is it right now?
It is November 30th, in the year 2011.
Who the hell are you?
During visitation, not
even a priest can...
Did you say 2011?
Does that mean we went back in time?
No, actually.
We have traveled far beyond that point.
With accelerated time, we've reached
a place humanity always winds up.
The end of the universe!
As in life, the ending of something
initiates a new beginning.
And that is what we call fate.
Even in the universe after this,
our planet will be
recreated and life on Earth
will follow the same path
that it was destined to.
And when humanity comes into existence,
it will be the beginning of a new dawn.
This is the promised age of happiness
brought forth by Maiden Heaven.
Bear witness to the new world!
What?
What is he even saying?
In this new world, the Jolyne
Cujo you knew exists no longer.
Neither do Jotaro, Anastasia, nor Hermes.
Not even their souls
survive total annihilation.
And that is because
the dead cannot return.
All of those who perish in the
accelerated time have been erased forever.
I left everyone who ever dared to interfere
with my destiny back in the other world.
All of them except for you, Emporio!
You were never supposed to
exist in this new reality!
So now I'm left with no other
choice but to eliminate you!
Destiny is mine!
I'm afraid that all of the future.
I'm not afraid of
sugar's rain of lies.
Itaami o no
eko elu tabi.
Kokoro wa eilu ni
togi Zoom sareru.
Cairo kae Zero Seiko
mei no sai hate ne?
Let's go.
Where is life?
Wie if it is?
Siege it with the future.
It's something that you can't do.
You can't do it.
No, no, no, no.
Code 909.
Security level 4.
Emergency alarm in the visiting room.
Inner door.
Code 909.
Security level 4.
Emergency alarm in the visiting room.
Inner door.
What's going on?
Dunno, but now's our chance.
Let's bounce!
Jolene broke out of prison last time too!
And now, it's the same but different!
That's fate at work.
This new universe has reached
this point in time after
repeating the same history
as the previous universe,
and it shall be the same Haruno.
Because that is fate, and fate is brought
on by certainty, not by coincidence.
For instance, your next move will be
to escape and try to hide in your room.
The very same room you used to
hide in in the previous universe.
Your secret room, as it was called.
The fact that you're going to retreat
here had already been decided.
It's no use!
to find somewhere other
than my room to hide!
How on earth did the prisoners
wind up in the common area?
Hell if I know, just move your ass!
Those guards are from before.
They're gonna fall.
What's wrong?
We're gonna fall.
If we keep going at this pace, we're
gonna end up having a nasty fall.
Huh?
What the hell are you talking about?
Well, uh, it just kinda came to me.
I'm not sure why, but it feels
like we're gonna fall somehow.
Don't tell me you're afraid!
Now get moving!
You want a pay cut?
How come?
For some reason I know too.
Both of those guards are going to...
Father, hi!
Can I help you?
Move it!
There's not a soul in this world!
Can escape their fate.
You most certainly will
be going to that room.
What is this?
What the heck is going on?
Right now we have traveled
far beyond that point.
With accelerated time
we have reached a place
humanity always winds
up the ultimate end of.
universe.
The end of the universe.
I remember reading about that
somewhere, in a book on the
beginning and end of all things.
Since the dawn of creation,
the universe continues to
expand, but at one point,
it starts to contract, almost as if you
are tightly squeezing a sponge ball.
When it can no longer contract, the
universe reaches its singularity point.
But there is a theory that the
Big Bang will repeat itself,
and a new universe will be
created to replace the old
Does this mean that we traveled
here from the previous world?
We made it all the way to the new 2011,
and at a tremendous speed
we journeyed through time as
the Earth progressed and
evolved at the same rapid pace.
But not everyone made the journey with us.
That is because the dead cannot return,
and all of those who perished in the
accelerated time have been erased forever.
They're not here.
Jolene and everyone else, they're gone.
I'm all alone, again.
The fortunate souls who were able to
transcend time have been blessed. No!
Those members of the human
race who survived have
experienced the future and
arrived at this new world.
The one truth of this universe is
that fate will always take its course.
And in turn, destiny will repeat itself.
When one human being meets
another, it is due to gravity.
They come together because
it was fated to be that way.
For example, what events will
unfold five years from now?
Thanks to their travels
through the accelerated time,
humanity has already experienced it.
They already know when
they'll get into an accident,
when they'll succumb to an illness,
and even when their life
will come to an end.
When will they meet and part with another?
Who will they fall in love with, and who
will they hate with a burning passion?
How many children will one bear, and what
kind of people will those children become?
When will war be declared, and when
will the world undergo a change?
They experience it as though
they're watching a movie.
So too will their children, and even
the generation that comes after.
Back in Cape Canaveral
is where it all began.
All of those who live through accelerated
time are aware of everything
that shall happen,
not because they saw it and memorized it,
but because it has been
engraved into their minds!
And that is how this world
will know true happiness
because they can be resolute
to face their future.
The ones who find this
resolve shall be truly happy.
You may think to yourself
why would I want to
know this would it not
just bring me despair?
But you're wrong.
Even if you knew that tomorrow was
your last day being prepared allows you
to go in peace because one's resolution
will eradicate all of that despair.
Humanity will be changed.
This is what we strove for.
Dio and I fought tirelessly to attain
heaven and now we're finally here.
Made in heaven is the future.
My gun.
Where is it?
Oh yeah.
I dropped it in the ocean.
If I might go right at the corner.
I'll come to a set of stairs and that's
where my ghost This room should be,
but Poochie already knows.
all about that room.
I need to go the other way.
Turn left, if I go this way
I can hide somewhere else.
Even if the smallest of
details might go astray,
Defeating fate is simply impossible.
Your only option now is running
away into your crack in the wall.
If I let you get away from me here,
and I end up losing track of you,
then you will most likely
try to defeat me later on.
That is the future that
is destined to happen.
So unfortunately for you,
I cannot let you live.
Even without the help of
Jolene and the others,
it is your fate to break
free from this prison,
as it is still my destiny to lose
sight of you at Cape Canaveral.
The reason I chose to
bring us here is because
it's before I sped up
time in Cape Canaveral.
Here I knew I could find
exactly where you were hiding.
The only chance I have to eliminate
you for good is right here and now.
That's why I elected
to stop the passing of
time at the moment you
were most vulnerable.
Now prepare yourself to die.
Only by accepting your death
can you be happy, Emporio.
Your only hope!
I do this now for the
sake of all humanity!
Die, Encario!
You see, fate is predetermined.
It can't be changed.
If that's true, then I'll just
have to make you change it for me.
When we were entering through
the crack in the wall,
your arm pushed this into my head.
In the final moments before
Weatherforecast died,
he turned a stand ability into a disc
before you landed the final blow.
And it's the same disc that
Jolene decided to entrust to me.
So I've been holding on
to it for both of them!
In the name of god i will
destroy you your actions
here today Emporio all
they have accomplished
is Solidifying the fact
that your screams will
become the trumpets of
hell even if you insert
someone Else's disc into
that mindless head of
yours whether's ability
is what it is because
of his Own talent do not
arrogantly assume that
you can just feel that
kind of power so easily
And besides, to stop you, I've
accelerated time once more!
In front of my honorable
ambitions, Emporio,
you shall come to realize your own
insignificance as you wither and fade away!
What is going on here I can't stand
something is wrong what is this madness
It's weather forecast one day I
read in a book that the deadliest
poison within proximity of any
organism is the air they breathe.
Every organism on this planet
needs oxygen to survive,
but the concentration level
of oxygen can't be above 40%.
100 % pure oxygen is extremely toxic, and
any life form exposed to it will perish.
Highly concentrated levels of oxygen
can corrode iron in a matter of seconds,
and even make fire explode.
It can also absorb
electrons in the human body,
slowly destroying the cell
tissues one after another.
If you breathe too much of it, Your
hands and feet will start to go numb?
and you won't be able to stand.
Plus, the tiny veins in your eyes
will snap and you'll go blind.
You can go ahead and
accelerate time all you want.
Weather forecast is a stand
that can control the weather.
I already used it to accumulate a massive
amount of pure oxygen into this room.
And now, you'll slowly lose consciousness,
as 100 % oxygen seeps deeper
and deeper into your tissues.
No, I refuse to let a
branch like you beat me!
I'm not the one in control here.
This is Weather Forecast's hidden ability.
You're the one who stole Weather's memory?
and the one who awakened him again!
when he regained his power
to project killer snails.
Father Poochie, it was all because of you.
Gravity still affects you, too.
You are unable to defeat your destiny.
No, you have to end this, Emporial.
You can still stop Weather.
Do not let him do this.
After I finally attained the
ability I've worked so hard for,
God wished it to be so!
It was an ability that God
chose for me to possess!
A new history of humanity will be born,
and the future of mankind will be saved!
We haven't even reached
the point in time yet
where time acceleration
started in Cape Canaveral.
Maiden Heaven has yet to be completed.
As long as it's after Cape Canaveral,
I will gladly sacrifice my life.
But if I die now,
I don't mean that everything I've done thus
far will have been utterly meaningless.
The fate of all humanity
will be changed forever.
If i die, people won't be able to see
their future as it happens before them?
which means they won't be
able to face their fate.
Don't you remember?
Accepting their fate is
how they'll be truly happy.
It was my mission to bring
about true happiness.
I cannot die here.
Don't you understand?
Fate won, and you are the loser.
You insignificant little.
I didn't do this alone.
Jolene knew I'd make it here, and this
is what she would've wanted me to do.
Brother 2, and FF, Ermes,
Anastasia, and even Mr. Jotaro.
We had no idea what the future
held, but we all had resolutions.
The one who couldn't accept
their own fate was you, Poochie.
True fate is walking
down the path of justice.
You're done for!
No, I'm not!
You're the one who doesn't
understand anything!
Go to hell, you insignificant little brat!
Oh, my God.
The bus
Give me a break I already told
you I've only got this 50 on me
Why don't you carry
change on the bus anyway
You're for real You gotta top
down Fine fine just hold up a sec
would ya I'm gonna go break this
50 at that gas station real quick
Oh, hey kid, you gettin' on this bus?
Talk about perfect timing.
You got any change?
I need to break this 50.
Yeah?
Is that good with you?
It ain't a counterfeit, trust me.
What the?
Don't leave me, dumbass!
Ah, just throw it back like that!
Hey!
Come on!
The bus went and drove off because your
response time was so freakin' slow!
I'm gonna wait two hours for the next one.
What the hell, man?
Ben!
Are you even listening to me?
Damn it.
Yeah, well, whatever.
That cheap prick probably thought I was a
fugitive from Green Dolphin or something.
You...
you are?
Huh?
Hey.
My car completely ran out of gas.
If you hook us up with some
gas and food with that 50,
I'll let you catch a ride
to wherever you want to go.
Same goes for you, kid.
Is that how you save on
travel expenses or something?
My sister used to always tell me to never
get in a car with some random stranger.
There's a storm on the way
too bad have fun getting
drenched while you wait
for the next bus to come!
But I don't think it's
letting up anytime soon.
Hop on in, kiddo.
It's okay, we're not bad people.
Call me Irene, and this
guy here is Anikis.
Where's your mom and dad at, bud?
We were actually just on our way
to visit my old man right now.
You see?
He's my boyfriend.
I don't know how things will turn out,
but if Dad approves of us being together,
then maybe we'll even get married.
Shit, man.
Is there really a storm heading this way?
I'll ride along, but ten bucks
is all you're getting from me.
I'm gonna have you guys make a
stop at Cape Canaveral, too, okay?
Come on, get in here.
We could really use your help.
Yeah, me too. To be honest.
You doing okay there, little boy?
Can you tell me your name?
Come on, I said to get in.
And I don't expect you to pay us either.
You're shaking like a tree.
Are you cold?
Here.
Emporio.
That's what you can call me, since
you wanted to know my name's Emporio.
Hey, look, there's a hitchhiker.
I'm not picking up another straggler.
Two is more than enough.
You're the one that said
there's a storm coming.
Come on, stop the car for the poor guy.
I'll be the roundabout.
The words will make you out and out.
And spend the day your way.
Call it morning driving through the sun.
And in and out the valley.
The music dance and sing.
They make the children really ring.
I spend the day your way.
Cold and morning driving through the sun.
And in and out the valley.
In and out around the lake.
Mountains come out of the sky.
And they stand there.
When my lover will be
there and we'll see you.
Ten and two summers will
be there laughing too.
Twenty and four before my lover will see.
I'll be there with you.
Thank you.